[Music]
I pile on the candy it's such a pretty
sight it makes the food taste Dandy but
my tummy hurts all night I'll put in some
ingredients but keep the rest for me I'm
not just disobedient I'm careful can't
you see it's a piece of cake to b a
pretty cake if the way is hazy you got
to do the cooking by the book you know
you can't be lazy
never use a m recipe the cake will end
up crazy if you do the cooking by the
book then you'll have a cake we got to
have it made you know that I love cake
finally it's time to make a
cake making food is just like science
with tools that blend and base and every
fun Appliance gives the food a different
taste it's a pizza cake to bake a pretty
cake if the way is hazy you got to do
the cooking by the book you know you
can't be lazy never use a messy recipe
the cake will end up crazy if you do the
cooking by the book then you'll have a
cake we got to have it made you know
that I love cake finally it's time to
make a cake we got to have it made you
know that I love cake
finally it's time to make a he got to do
the cooking by the book
[Music]